adplotter.com 2016-05-06

# Adplotter.com :: Privacy Policy

#### 1.1 What Our Privacy policy Covers

Our privacy policy covers how we treat personal information that we collect when registering for Adplotter Marketing Services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

#### 1.2 Information Collection and Security Policy

We collect personal information about you when registering a Adplotter Marketing Services client account. This personal information is information about you, such as your name, address, email address or phone number. This information is only used to identify your registration or webstore purchase and to contact you in case we have a question about your registration or purchase. We will never see or store your credit card information as every webstore purchase is processed with secure 128-bit encryption.

#### 1.3 Information Sharing and Disclosure

Adplotter does not sell, rent or share your personal information to anybody. Cookies may be placed on your computer as part of the shopping check-out procedure.

#### 1.4 Changes to this privacy policy

We may occasionally update our privacy policy. When we do, we will place a notice on our website to inform you  

_**You can also contact our customer service by mailing to:**_

Adplotter  
85 NE Loop 410  
Suite 616  
San Antonio, TX. 78216 

All refunds will be provided as a credit to the credit card used when purchasing your Adplotter Marketing Services. Refunds are issued within 5 days of company approval.
